byreferralonly.com 2004-12-07

# By Referral Only®

  | **Our Commitment to Privacy.**  
Your privacy is very important to us at By Referral Only, Inc. ("www.byreferralonly.com"). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site (the "Site"). 

**Your Consent.**  
By using this Site, you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. www.byreferralonly.com’s Privacy Policy applies to individuals who use our Site and we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy, along with related procedures, at any time. 

**Collection, Use and Retention of User Information.**  
When you visit our Site you may provide us with two types of information: 1) personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis; and 2) web site use information collected as you browse our Site.

  1. **Personal Information -- Our Use of Information That You Provide Us.**
    1. **General Policy.**  
Broadly speaking, we may use your personal information for purposes of administering our business activities and providing you with newsletters and other information and updates. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our users’ personal information. If you desire not to receive these commercial electronic communications from us you may click the link provided at the bottom of the such emails or contact our privacy officer listed below.
  2. **Web Site Use Information.**  
Similar to other commercial web sites, our Site may utilize a standard technology called "Cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our Site is used. 
    1. **What Are Cookies?**  
"Cookies" are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a web site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on the user's hard drive. Information gathered through Cookies and web server logs may include information such as the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the Site, and the web sites visited just before and just after our Site. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from web page to web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. 
    2. **How We Use Information We Collect from Cookies.**  
We may use web site browser software tools such as Cookies and web server logs to gather information about our Site users' browsing activities in order to constantly improve our Site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Site to better meet the needs of our members and prospective members. Since www.byreferralonly.com uses temporary Cookies, they will be deleted when you close your browser program. 
  3. **Disclosure of Information.**
    1. **Generally.**  
Any communication or material you transmit to the Site, other than non-public personally identifiable information, by electronic mail or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments or suggestions or the like is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and non-proprietary. Anything you transmit or post, other than non-public personally identifiable information, becomes the property of www.byreferralonly.com and may be used for any purpose, including, but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcasting and posting. 
    2. **Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information.**  
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. 
    3. **Sharing Information with Third Parties.**  
From time to time, you may notice offers from www.byreferralonly.com’s sponsors and others outside companies listed on our Site. We cannot and do not make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies, and are not responsible in any way for how these companies use Cookies or any other information you provide to them. 
    4. **Sharing Information with Strategic Partners.**  
We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and e-mail for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships, we will retain all ownership rights to the information, and we will not share information regarding your personal financial data.
  4. **Other Web Sites Linked to Our Site.**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by web sites linked to or from our Site nor the information or content contained therein. This remains true even when the linked site appears within the parameters or window/frame of our Site. Often links to other web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Site. 

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Site to another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

  5. **E-mail This Article.**  
If you enter personally identifiable information in the "E-mail This Article" link located throughout our Site, this information is used solely to generate a one-time e-mail to the recipient you designate. This information is not stored in our database for future use. 
  6. **Security.**  
This Site takes reasonable precautions to protect your information. When our order forms prompt you to enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number), your information is encrypted. By Referral Only, Inc. is [certified to process secure transactions](https://digitalid.verisign.com/as2/d2ca4004ed4ed2d0a0a4afd03d2515f3) by VeriSign. 
  7. **Message Boards.**  
The message boards provided on this Site are free forums for the exchange of ideas and information within the By Referral Only Community and are not intended to be used as a vehicle for advertising or mass e-mailing by said community. Users of the message boards are subject to the conditions of the Terms of Use Agreement. Please use discretion whenever disclosing personal information on the message boards. While every reasonable effort will be made to monitor the content within the message board system, www.byreferralonly.com reserves the right to edit, delete and modify postings in its sole discretion, it cannot and shall not be responsible for monitoring such message content. www.byreferralonly.com expressly disclaims all liability for information posted on such message boards. By Referral Only, Inc. shall not be responsible for information posted by its members. 
  8. **Children's Privacy.**  
Our Site is not intended for the use of children. We do not knowingly market to, or solicit data from, children. 
  9. **Questions/Concerns.**  
If you would like to review, edit or delete any of the information we have collected from you, or if you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact: 

> Terry Hunefeld, President and Chief Executive Officer  
>  By Referral Only, Inc.
